A Guide to the Asia Society records FA110
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Director of Education and Communications, Timothy Plummer Files, 1972-1984; 10
  - Testimony to Congressional Subcommittee on Reauthorization of Title VI, 1979 (Box 654, Folder 6397)
  - American Council on the Teaching of Foreign Languages, 1980-1981 (Box 654, Folder 6398)
  - National Council on Foreign Language and International Studies, 1980 (Box 654, Folder 6399)
  - Council of Chief State School Officers, 1977-1979 (Box 654, Folder 6400)
  - National Council for the Social Studies, 1979-1982 (Box 654, Folder 6401)
  - North Carolina Council on International Education, 1980 (Box 654, Folder 6402)
  - NY Council for the Humanities, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 6403)
  - World Affairs Council of Pennsylvania, 1982-1983 (Box 654, Folder 6404)
  - NY State Education Department (Abromowitz and Ferguson), 1972-1980 (Box 654, Folder 6405)
  - Asian Culture Centre for UNESCO, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 6406)
  - Global Perspectives, 1979-1983 (Box 654, Folder 6407)
  - International Film Foundation, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 6408)
  - Metropolitan Consortium, 1980 (Box 654, Folder 6409)
  - Learning through Expanded Arts Program (LEAP), 1981 (Box 655, Folder 6410)
  - National Foundation for Improvement in Education, 1980 (Box 655, Folder 6411)
  - NY Urban Coalition (Lynn H. Gray, Jr.), 1983 (Box 655, Folder 6412)
  - Correspondence - Constantina Bailly, 1984 (Box 655, Folder 6413)
  - Association for Asian Studies (AAS), 1982 (Box 655, Folder 6414)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities (AASCU), 1983 (Box 655, Folder 6415)
  - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1982-1983 (Box 655, Folder 6416)
  - Association for Educational Communications and Technology, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 6417)
  - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development (ASCD), 1982-1983 (Box 655, Folder 6418)
  - American Library Association, American Association of School Librarians (ALA, AASL), 1983 (Box 655, Folder 6419)
  - MCSS-New England Conference on Teaching and Learning, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 6420)
  - National Association of Elementary and Secondary School Principals, 1982-1983 (Box 655, Folder 6421)
  - NEA Conference, Philadelphia, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 6422)
  - PTA Cnference, Las Vegas, 1984 (Box 655, Folder 6423)
  - Lisle Fellowship, 1982-1983 (Box 655, Folder 6424)
- Administration, 1956-1987; 11
  Series 11: Administration
  Subseries 1: General
  Subseries 2: Corporate Programs
  Subseries 3: Executive Department Files
  Subseries 4: Director of Public Affairs, Marshall M. Bouton (MMB) Files
  Subseries 5: Asia Society Executive Vice President, Lionel Landry Files
  Subseries 6: Asia Society President, Phillips Talbot papers
  Subseries 7: Director, Meetings and Studies Program, Herbert D. Spivack Files
  Subseries 8: Asia Society Board of Trustees
  See also: Series 7.
  - General, 1
    - Administration, Memos, 1970 (Box 668, Folder 6494)
    - Administration - Correspondence, Meetings and Studies, 1974-1976 (Box 668, Folder 6495)
    - Administration - Correspondence, Meetings and Studies, 1974-1976 (Box 668, Folder 6496)
    - Administration - Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 668, Folder 6497)
    - Administration - Correspondence, Meetings and Studies, 1975 July-December (Box 668, Folder 6498)
    - Administration - Correspondence, Meetings and Studies, 1975 January-June (Box 668, Folder 6499)
    - Administration - Correspondence, Meetings and Studies, 1974 (Box 668, Folder 6500)
    - Administration - Correspondence, Meetings and Studies, 1974 (Box 668, Folder 6501)
    - Administration - Correspondence, Meetings and Studies, 1973 July-December (Box 669, Folder 6502)
    - Administration - Correspondence, Meetings and Studies, 1973 January-June (Box 669, Folder 6503)
    - Administration, Meetings Studies - Correspondence, Kempton Dunn, 1971-1972 (Box 669, Folder 6504)
    - Administration, Meetings Studies - Correspondence, Kempton Dunn, 1973 (Box 669, Folder 6505)
    - Administration, Meetings Studies - Correspondence, Kempton Dunn, 1974-1975 (Box 669, Folder 6506)
    - Administration, Porter McKeever / Phillips Talbot, 1970-1972 (Box 669, Folder 6507)
    - By-laws, 1972 (Box 669, Folder 6508)
    - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1961, 1968, 1972 (Box 669, Folder 6509)
    - Minutes, Members and Trustees, 1971-1972 (Box 670, Folder 6510)
    - Minutes, Contempary Arts Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 670, Folder 6511)
    - Mintues, Mass Media and Asia Committee, 1966 (Box 670, Folder 6512)
    - Minutes, Education Committee, 1963 (Box 670, Folder 6513)
    - Minutes, Asian Literature Program Advisory Program, 1971 (Box 670, Folder 6514)
    - Minutes, Publications Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 670, Folder 6515)
    - Administration, Program needs, 1971 (Box 670, Folder 6516)
    - Minutes, Gallery Committee, 1961 (Box 670, Folder 6517)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Supplemental material, 1962 (Box 755, Folder 7263)
    - Operating Fund - Cash Receipts ledger, 1963-1964 (Box 755, Folder 7264)
    - Performing Arts Program - Receipts and Disbursements Ledger, 1963-1964 (Box 755, Folder 7265)
    - Operating Fund - Cash Disbursements, 1964-1965 (Box 755, Folder 7266)
    - Operating Fund - Cash Receipts, 1964-1965 (Box 755, Folder 7267)
    - Operating Fund - Cash Disbursements, 1965-1966 (Box 755, Folder 7268)
    - Asia Society Sales, 1966-1967 (Box 755, Folder 7269)
    - Capital Expenditures, 1957-1970 (Box 755, Folder 7271)
    - General Ledger - Income and Expenditure Accounts, 1957-1958 (Box 756, Folder 7272)
    - Journal, 1956-1961 (Box 756, Folder 7273)
    - General Journal, 1961 (Box 756, Folder 7274)
    - General Journal, 1960 (Box 756, Folder 7275)
    - Operating Fund - General Ledger, 1959 (Box 757, Folder 7276)
    - Operating Fund - General Ledger, 1962-1963 (Box 757, Folder 7277)
    - Operating Fund - General Ledger, 1963-1964 (Box 757, Folder 7278)
    - Operating Fund - General Ledger, 1964-1965 (Box 757, Folder 7279)
    - Accountant's Report, 1961 June 30 (Box 758, Folder 7280)
    - Accountant's Report, 1962 June 30 (Box 758, Folder 7281)
    - Accountant's Report, 1963 June 30 (Box 758, Folder 7282)
    - Accountant's Report, 1964 June 30 (Box 758, Folder 7283)
    - Accountant's Report, 1965 June 30 (Box 758, Folder 7284)
    - Accountant's Report, 1965 February 28 (Box 758, Folder 7285)
    - Accountant's Report, 1971 June 30 (Box 758, Folder 7286)
    - Accountant's Report, 1957 December 31 (Box 758, Folder 7287)
    - Mekong Project (Committee for Coordination of investigations of the Lower McKong Basin) - Seminar, 1973 October 29 (Box 758, Folder 7288)
    - Mekong Project (Committee for Coordination of investigations of the Lower McKong Basin) - Publications, 1968, 1972 (Box 758, Folder 7289)
    - Mekong Project (Committee for Coordination of investigations of the Lower McKong Basin) - Semi-Annual Report (Vols. I - II) -, 1973 January 1-June 30 (Box 758, Folder 7290)
    - Mekong Project (Committee for Coordination of investigations of the Lower McKong Basin) - Report on Indicative Basin Plan (Box 758, Folder 7291)
    - Accountant's Report - Financial Statements, 1958 December 31 (Box 758, Folder 7292)
    - Membership Reports, 1957-1969 June (Box 758, Folder 7293)
    - Personnel - Death Benefit and Retirement Plan, 1957-1961 (Box 759, Folder 7294)
      Restricted from scholarly access - Personnel material.
    - Personnel - Death Benefit and Retirement Plan, 1957-1961 (Box 759, Folder 7295)
    - Personnel - Death Benefit and Retirement Plan, 1957-1961 (Box 759, Folder 7296)
    - Personnel - Death benefits and retirement plan, 1962-1967 (Box 759, Folder 7297)
    - Personnel - Death benefits and retirement plan, 1962-1967 (Box 759, Folder 7298)
    - Personnel - Death benefits and retirement plan, 1962-1967 (Box 759, Folder 7299)
    - Personnel - Death benefits and retirement plan, 1962-1967 (Box 759, Folder 7300)
    - Personnel - Death benefits and retirement plan, 1962-1967 (Box 759, Folder 7301)
  - Corporate Programs, 2
    - Corporate Programs - Business Council Day File, 1979 (Box 670, Folder 6518)
    - Corporate Programs- Business Council Day File, 1980 (Box 670, Folder 6519)
    - Corporate Programs - Business Council Day File, 1981 (Box 670, Folder 6520)
    - Corporate Programs - Chronological File, 1983 January-June (Box 670, Folder 6521)
    - Corporate Programs - Chronological File, 1983 July-December (Box 671, Folder 6522)
    - Corporate Programs - Chronological File, 1984 January-June (Box 671, Folder 6523)
    - Corporate Programs - Chronological File, 1984 July-December (Box 671, Folder 6524)
    - Corporate Programs - Chronological File, 1985 January-June (Box 672, Folder 6525)
    - Corporate Programs - Chronological File, 1985 July-December (Box 672, Folder 6526)
    - Corporate Programs - India - General, 1983-1984 (Box 672, Folder 6527)
    - Corporate Programs - Barnes Lunch, 1983-1984 (Box 672, Folder 6528)
    - Corporate Programs - Japan Conference - Guest List, 1983 May 6 (Box 672, Folder 6529)
    - Corporate Programs - Other Conference Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 672, Folder 6530)
    - Corporate Programs - Luncheon, Prime Minister Mahathir bin Mohamid, 1982 September 28 (Box 672, Folder 6531)
    - Corporate Programs - Keatley Discussion, 1983 September 13 (Box 672, Folder 6532)
    - Corporate Programs - Annual Corporate Dinner, 1983 September 22 (Box 673, Folder 6533)
    - Corporate Programs - Dhanabala Program, 1983 September 29 (Box 673, Folder 6534)
    - Corporate Programs - Drysdale Luncheon, 1983 October 7 (Box 673, Folder 6535)
    - Corporate Programs - Bailey Discussion, 1983 October 12 (Box 673, Folder 6536)
    - Corporate Programs - Zysman Luncheon, 1983 October 21 (Box 673, Folder 6537)
    - Corporate Programs - Willenson Program, 1983 November 1 (Box 673, Folder 6538)
    - Corporate Programs - Agricultural Panel, 1983 November 15 (Box 673, Folder 6539)
    - Corporate Programs - U.S.-Pakistan Conference, 1983 November (Box 673, Folder 6540)
    - Corporate Programs - Malaysia Program, 1984 January 16 (Box 673, Folder 6541-6542)
    - Corporate Programs - U.S.- Korea Society, Far East-American Council on The Asia Society Luncheon with Dr. Nam, Duck Woo, Chr. Korea Traders Association, 1984 January 18 (Box 674, Folder 6543)
    - Corporate Programs - Corporate Council Meeting, 1984 January 30 (Box 674, Folder 6544)
    - Corporate Programs - Wolfowitz Lunch, 1984 January 31 (Box 674, Folder 6545)
    - Corporate Programs - Ortner Program, 1984 (Box 674, Folder 6546)
    - Corporate Programs - Korea Trade Mission Lunch, 1984 March 1 (Box 674, Folder 6547)
    - Corporate Programs - High Tech Conference, 1984 April (Box 674, Folder 6548-6549)
    - Corporate Programs - Korea Briefing, 1984 April 10 (Box 675, Folder 6550)
    - Corporate Programs - Korea Briefing, 1984 April 10 (Box 675, Folder 6551)
    - Corporate Programs - Ambassador Smith, Michael B., Deputy U.S. Trade Rep, 1983 (Box 675, Folder 6552)
    - Corporate Programs -Thai Delegation, 1984 (Box 675, Folder 6553)
    - Corporate Programs - Lee Morgan Luncheon, 1984 April (Box 675, Folder 6554)
    - Corporate Programs - Masaya Miyoshi Program, 1984 May (Box 675, Folder 6555)
    - Corporate Programs - Thailand Country Briefing, 1984 May (Box 676, Folder 6556)
    - Corporate Programs - Indian Finance Luncheon, 1984 September 17 (Box 676, Folder 6557)
    - Corporate Programs - Korea Finance minister, 1984 (Box 676, Folder 6558)
    - Corporate Programs - Corporate Council Meeting, 1984 September 21 (Box 676, Folder 6559)
    - Corporate Programs - Nesen Luncheon, 1984 October 1 (Box 676, Folder 6560)
    - Corporate Programs - Davies Luncheon, 1984 October (Box 676, Folder 6561)
    - Corporate Programs - Chinese Textile Program, 1984 November (Box 676, Folder 6562)
    - Corporate Programs - Hong Kong Conference, 1984 October (Box 676, Folder 6563)
    - Corporate Programs - Ambassador Holdridge Lunch, 1984 October (Box 676, Folder 6564)
    - Corporate Programs - Country Briefing - Taiwan, 1984 November 1 (Box 676, Folder 6565)
    - Corporate Programs - Yen Conference: An International Yen: What's Ahead for Asia, 1984 November 14 (Box 677, Folder 6566)
    - Corporate Programs - Gottliebsen Lunch - Australia-U.S. Business Relationships, 1984 November 16 (Box 677, Folder 6567)
    - Corporate Programs - Fairbanks Luncheon, 1984 November 28 (Box 677, Folder 6568)
    - Corporate Programs - Stern Luncheon - Trade Relations - U.S., Japan and the NIC, 1984 December 10 (Box 677, Folder 6569)
  - Executive Department Files, 3
    - Executive Department Files - Houston Center, 1984 (Box 677, Folder 6570)
    - Executive Department Files - Southern California, 1983-1986 (Box 677, Folder 6571)
    - Executive Department Files - Washington Center, 1984-1985 (Box 678, Folder 6572)
    - Executive Department Files - Regional Centers Meeting, 1984 December 13 (Box 678, Folder 6573)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 678, Folder 6574)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 678, Folder 6575)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 678, Folder 6576)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 679, Folder 6577)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 679, Folder 6578)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 679, Folder 6579)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 679, Folder 6580)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 680, Folder 6581)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 680, Folder 6582)
    - Executive Department Files - Asia Magazine Restructuring, 1982-1983 (Box 680, Folder 6583)
    - Executive Department Files - RBO - Asia Magazine, 1982-1983 (Box 680, Folder 6584)
    - Executive Department Files - Publications, 1984 (Box 680, Folder 6585)
    - Executive Department Files - Publications, 1984 (Box 681, Folder 6586)
    - Executive Department Files - Performing Arts, 1984 (Box 681, Folder 6587)
    - Executive Department Files - Performing Arts, 1984 (Box 681, Folder 6588)
    - Executive Department Files - Galleries, 1984 (Box 681, Folder 6589)
    - Executive Department Files - Galleries, 1984 (Box 681, Folder 6590)
    - Executive Department Files - Galleries, 1984 (Box 681A, Folder 6591)
    - Executive Department Files - Finance and Administration, 1984 (Box 681A, Folder 6592)
    - Executive Department Files - Finance and Administration, 1984 (Box 681A, Folder 6593)
    - Executive Department Files - Education and Communications, 1984 (Box 681A, Folder 6594)
    - Executive Department Files - Development, 1984 (Box 682, Folder 6595)
    - Executive Department Files - Development, 1984 (Box 682, Folder 6596)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1985 (Box 682, Folder 6597)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1985 (Box 682, Folder 6598)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1985 (Box 683, Folder 6599)
    - Executive Department Files - Publications, 1985 (Box 683, Folder 6600)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1985 (Box 683, Folder 6601)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1985 (Box 683, Folder 6602)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1985 (Box 684, Folder 6603)
    - Executive Department Files - Tokyo Meeting - General, 1985 May (Box 684, Folder 6604)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1985 (Box 684, Folder 6605)
    - Executive Department Files - Performing Arts, 1985 (Box 684, Folder 6606)
    - Executive Department Files - Galleries, 1985 (Box 685, Folder 6607)
    - Executive Department Files - Galleries, 1985 (Box 685, Folder 6608-6609)
    - Executive Department Files - Finance and Administration, 1985 (Box 685, Folder 6610-6611)
    - Executive Department Files - Education and Communications, 1985 (Box 686, Folder 6612)
    - Executive Department Files - Education, 1985 (Box 686, Folder 6613)
    - Executive Department Files - Development, 1985 (Box 686, Folder 6614)
    - Executive Department Files - Development, 1985 (Box 686, Folder 6615)
    - Executive Department Files - Bookstore, 1985 (Box 686, Folder 6616)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1985 January-February (Box 687, Folder 6617-6618)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1985 March (Box 687, Folder 6619)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1985 April (Box 687, Folder 6620)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1985 May (Box 687, Folder 6621)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1985 June (Box 687, Folder 6622)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1985 July (Box 687, Folder 6623)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1985 August (Box 688, Folder 6624)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1985 September (Box 688, Folder 6625)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1985 October-November (Box 688, Folder 6626)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1985 December (Box 688, Folder 6627)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1986 January (Box 688, Folder 6628)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1986 February-March (Box 688, Folder 6629)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1986 April (Box 689, Folder 6630)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1986 May (Box 689, Folder 6631)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1986 June-July (Box 689, Folder 6632)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1986 August-September (Box 689, Folder 6633)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1986 October-November (Box 689, Folder 6634)
    - Executive Department - Chronological Files, 1986 December (Box 689, Folder 6635)
    - Executive Department Files - Washington Center - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1982 September 16 (Box 689, Folder 6636)
    - Executive Department Files - Los Angeles Center - So. California Advisory Council, 1982 (Box 689, Folder 6637)
    - Executive Department Files - Houston Center, 1982 (Box 690, Folder 6638)
    - Executive Department Files - Washington Center, 1982 (Box 690, Folder 6639)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1982 (Box 690, Folder 6640)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1982 (Box 690, Folder 6641)
    - Executive Department Files - Film and Broadcast Dept., 1982 (Box 690, Folder 6642)
    - Executive Department Files - Performing Arts, 1981-1982 (Box 691, Folder 6643)
    - Executive Department Files - Gallery, 1982 (Box 691, Folder 6644)
    - Executive Department Files - Film and Broadcast Unit, 1982 (Box 691, Folder 6645)
    - Executive Department Files - Education, 1982 (Box 691, Folder 6646)
    - Executive Department Files - China Council, 1982 (Box 691, Folder 6647)
    - Executive Department Files - Asia Magazine, 1982 (Box 692, Folder 6648)
    - Executive Department Files - Volunteers, 1983 (Box 692, Folder 6649)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1983 (Box 692, Folder 6650)
    - Executive Department Files - Public Affairs, 1983 (Box 692, Folder 6651)
    - Executive Department Files - Publications, 1983 (Box 692, Folder 6652)
    - Executive Department Files - Publications, 1983 (Box 693, Folder 6653-6654)
    - Executive Department Files - Performing Arts, 1983 (Box 693, Folder 6655)
    - Executive Department Files - Indo-U.S. Subcommission, 1983 (Box 693, Folder 6656)
    - Executive Department Files - Gallery - Attendance and Minutes, 1983 (Box 693, Folder 6657)
    - Executive Department Files - Gallery, 1983 (Box 693, Folder 6658)
    - Executive Department Files - Gallery, 1983 (Box 694, Folder 6659)
    - Executive Department Files - Finance and Administration, 1983 (Box 694, Folder 6660)
    - Executive Department Files - Education and Communications, 1983 (Box 694, Folder 6661)
    - Executive Department Files - Education and Communications, 1983 (Box 694, Folder 6662)
    - Executive Department Files - Education and Communications, 1983 (Box 694, Folder 6663)
    - Executive Department Files - Education and Communications, 1983 (Box 695, Folder 6664)
    - Executive Department Files - Development, 1983 (Box 695, Folder 6665)
    - Executive Department Files - Book Store, 1983 (Box 695, Folder 6666)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Queen of Thailand Visit, 1981 November 11 (Box 695, Folder 6667)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Thai Bicentennial, 1981-1982 (Box 695, Folder 6668)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Chiefs Luncheon, 1982 January 12 (Box 695, Folder 6669)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Development in the Pacific Islands, 1982 January 20 (Box 695, Folder 6670)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Social Studies Supervisors Association, 1982 March 17 (Box 695, Folder 6671)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Reception for Volunteers, 1982 April 14 (Box 695, Folder 6672)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Margaret Ton's Concert, 1982 April 17 (Box 695, Folder 6673)
    - Asia Soceity Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Ambassador Edward Maters "Indonesia: Reflections on Four Years in Jakarta", 1982 April 21 (Box 695, Folder 6674)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Performing Arts Fashion Benefit, 1982 May 3 (Box 695, Folder 6675)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Fox Butterfield's Lecture/Reception, 1982 May 11 (Box 695, Folder 6676)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Phillips Talbot, JDR 3rd Memorial Lectures, 1982 May 19 (Box 695, Folder 6677)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Indira Gandhi Speech, Luncheon - FPA, 1982 August 2 (Box 695, Folder 6678)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Wenner-Gren Foundation International Theatre and Ritual Symposium, 1982 August 24 (Box 696, Folder 6679)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Fletcher Conference on Thailand, 1982 (Box 696, Folder 6680)
    - Executive Programs - Dinner for Gen. Zia of Pakistan (David Rockefeller sponsor-Chase), 1982 December 9 (Box 696, Folder 6681)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - HK-Shanghai Bank Reception, 1982 December 15 (Box 696, Folder 6682)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Feature film "Dr. Norman Bethune", 1983 December 15 (Box 696, Folder 6683)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Indonesian Film Festival, 1983 March 18 (Box 696, Folder 6684)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Tony Paul, Business Council luncheon, 1983 May 18 (Box 696, Folder 6685)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - "Asian Business Trends: the Journalist's Perspective", 1983 September 13 (Box 696, Folder 6686)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - "Discover Indonesia" Dinner, 1983 October 4 (Box 696, Folder 6687)
    - Executive Programs - Chase Manhattan's Party, 1983 October 23 (Box 696, Folder 6688)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Korean Evening, Performing Arts Benefit, 1983 November 17 (Box 696, Folder 6689)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Reception for Asian Consul Generals, 1983 December 15 (Box 696, Folder 6690)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Preview of Korean Folk Art, Higher Category Members, 1983 December 6 (Box 696, Folder 6691)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Dinner, Korean Folk Art Exhibit, 1983 December 6 (Box 696, Folder 6692)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - TAS/Fletcher Conference on "Indonesia and the U.S.", 1983 October 6-8 (Box 696, Folder 6693)
    - Executive Programs - Asia Society Event - Papua - New Guinea Film and Reception - Asia Society-Julliard-Bechtel, 1984 March 7 (Box 696, Folder 6694)